CHARLIE MASON

Undergraduate Gameplay Programmer

**** 07747867911

@ charlie.mason020@gmail.com

_ළ charliemason.net

SUMMARY

I'm an undergraduate with key skills in Unreal Engine and C++ soon to graduate in 2023. I'm particularly interested in games design especially focused on gameplay engineering, I enjoy learning how to create new game mechanics and systems that add to the player's experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Designer, Web Developer

iii 01/2023 - Present ♀ Remote

Building a website portfolio to present myself and projects

- Created the different pages using HTML
- Developed the pages with CSS to improve the visual aspects
- Small Javascript implementation for loading screen animation between

Gameplay Tester & Recorder Freelancing

Axia Labs, Upwork

= 11/2022 - 02/2023

Remote

Recorded high quality gameplay from battle simulator games consisting of (Ultimate Epic Battle Simulator 2, TABS, Overgrown, Insurgency: Sandstorm)

Live Streamer, Content Creator

Online media videography company

Twitch

= 06/2020 - 02/2023

Remote

Created professional live streams each week to an audience online. Edited and published videos to follow these live streams

- Presented live streams multiple times a week, consisting of gameplay with commentary
- Built a community through social media with posts in different gaming communities and community servers
- Organised channel events with rewards through the community
- Weekly video uploads with edited gameplay and commentary

EDUCATION

BSc Games Development

Norwich University of the Arts

UAL Level 3 Extended Diploma in Games Design & Animation

Chelmsford College

= 09/2018 - 06/2020

♦ Chelmsford, United Kingdom

UAL Level 2 Diploma in creative media production and technology

Chelmsford College

SKILLS

Python Blender HTML Microsoft Office Suite Unity C++ C# **Unreal Engine 4/5** Git Java **CSS Photoshop Premiere Pro After Effects**

STRENGTHS

Flexibility

Committed to new projects or helping others work to complete tasks efficiently, either in remote or office locations.



Results Driven

Devoted to the key goals, delivering workloads with excellent quality and within time contraints.



Enthusiastic Learner

Enthusiastic to learn new coding languages or methods of improving performance, always seeking to improve my skill set.

ACHIEVEMENTS



Released Game

Produced and published my own game over the last 4 months of my university course, frequently updating it with new content, the game has received praise by players.



My Personal Website!

Developed and created my first website using HTML and CSS, frequently updating.



Professional Pitch

Participated with other students to develop a basic game and pitch presentation for a games studio within a short deadline. This was well received by the company, they advised we would get funding for this.